I like to think that in a situation, I would like know what to do, but I think that's what
it is.
Honestly, it's really not, you're not really thinking it's not a full doubt out process.
It's really like moment, moment, moment, moment, moment.
You know what I mean?
Like, and like you said, oh yeah, you say like, yeah, that happened.
But honestly, if I'm going to die, I'm going to fight for my life.
Like that's what it is.
Like I'm out of here.
You're not about to hold me hostage.
I seen a man had already lost his life at that point.
I, I need to get out of here by any means possible.
He's not going to let me run while he still has a gun.
So the only thing I can think of was getting rid of the threat and the threat was that gun.